export const chapter = "Chapter - 8: states of Matter";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "What are the three main properties of a solid?",
          optionA: "Definite shape, definite mass, definite volume",
          optionB: "Definite shape, indefinite mass, definite volume",
          optionC: "Indefinite shape, definite mass, definite volume",
          correctAnswer: "Definite shape, definite mass, definite volume",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which state of matter does not have a definite shape, mass, and volume?",
          optionA: "Solid",
          optionB: "Liquid",
          optionC: "Gas",
          correctAnswer: "Gas",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What happens to a liquid when it changes into a solid through cooling?",
          optionA: "Freezing",
          optionB: "Melting",
          optionC: "Evaporation",
          correctAnswer: "Freezing",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When a solid changes into a liquid by gaining heat, what is the process called?",
          optionA: "Condensation",
          optionB: "Freezing",
          optionC: "Melting",
          correctAnswer: "Melting",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which state of matter takes the shape of its container and does not have a definite shape?",
          optionA: "Solid",
          optionB: "Liquid",
          optionC: "Gas",
          correctAnswer: "Liquid",
        },
        {
          question: "What happens when a gas changes into a liquid on cooling?",
          optionA: "Melting",
          optionB: "Evaporation",
          optionC: "Condensation",
          correctAnswer: "Condensation",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the context of matter, what is the definition of matter?",
          optionA: "Anything with a definite shape and volume",
          optionB:
            "Anything with mass, occupies space, and can be felt by sense organs",
          optionC: "Anything that can change states",
          correctAnswer:
            "Anything with mass, occupies space, and can be felt by sense organs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which state of matter always looks the same and takes up the same amount of space?",
          optionA: "Solid",
          optionB: "Liquid",
          optionC: "Gas",
          correctAnswer: "Solid",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the process called when a liquid changes into a gas by gaining heat?",
          optionA: "Melting",
          optionB: "Freezing",
          optionC: "Evaporation",
          correctAnswer: "Evaporation",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When a gas changes into a liquid on cooling, what is the process called?",
          optionA: "Condensation",
          optionB: "Evaporation",
          optionC: "Freezing",
          correctAnswer: "Condensation",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "A solid has a definite __________.",
          optionA: "Mass",
          optionB: "Volume",
          optionC: "Shape",
          correctAnswer: "Shape",
        },
        {
          question: "A liquid does not have a definite __________.",
          optionA: "Mass",
          optionB: "Volume",
          optionC: "Shape",
          correctAnswer: "Shape",
        },
        {
          question: "A gas does not have a definite __________.",
          optionA: "Mass",
          optionB: "Volume",
          optionC: "Shape",
          correctAnswer: "Shape",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When a liquid changes into a solid through cooling, the process is called __________.",
          optionA: "Freezing",
          optionB: "Melting",
          optionC: "Evaporation",
          correctAnswer: "Freezing",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When a solid changes into a liquid by gaining heat, the process is called __________.",
          optionA: "Condensation",
          optionB: "Freezing",
          optionC: "Melting",
          correctAnswer: "Melting",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When a gas changes into a liquid on cooling, the process is called __________.",
          optionA: "Condensation",
          optionB: "Evaporation",
          optionC: "Freezing",
          correctAnswer: "Condensation",
        },
        {
          question: "Matter includes both __________ and non-living things.",
          optionA: "Alive",
          optionB: "Living",
          optionC: "Live",
          correctAnswer: "Living",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The three states of matter can be changed from one form to another through the process of __________.",
          optionA: "Sublimation",
          optionB: "Transformation",
          optionC: "Change of States",
          correctAnswer: "Change of States",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Water (liquid) changed into ice (solid) is an example of __________.",
          optionA: "Melting",
          optionB: "Freezing",
          optionC: "Evaporation",
          correctAnswer: "Freezing",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When a gas changes into liquid on cooling, the process is called __________.",
          optionA: "Melting",
          optionB: "Evaporation",
          optionC: "Condensation",
          correctAnswer: "Condensation",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "A solid does not have a definite shape.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "A liquid takes the shape of its container.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "A gas has a definite volume.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Freezing is the process of a liquid changing into a gas.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Melting is the process of a solid changing into a liquid.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Condensation is the process of a gas changing into a liquid.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Matter includes only non-living things.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The three states of matter cannot be changed from one form to another.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Evaporation is the process of a liquid changing into a gas.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Condensation is the process of a gas changing into a solid.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
